FPSRussia经典高清重制计划 第一集
字幕：罗兹  时间轴：罗兹  压制：罗兹
本作发布日期为
2011年4月25日
Hello my friends this is FPSRussia
大家好欢迎收看FPSRussia的大枪秀
I have something really nice for you today
今天给大家准备了个好东西
This is the AA-12
这 就是AA-12
It's a fully automatic 12-gauge shotgun
全自动 12号霰弹口径
It's a military weapon
军用武器
You're getting 300 rpm
射速达到每分钟300发
And the thing about this gun: it's complete stainless steel construction
而且全不锈钢结构
And you don't need to clean it
不用清洁
You don't need to lubricate it
油都不用上
It just keeps going no matter what
这玩意可以一直射到死
In any weather condition, whether you are a Marine
而且在各种环境下 不管你是陆战队
or you're a SEAL coming out of the ocean
或者是特种部队 上天入地
everything joints
到哪都很适用
This is a magazine that gets 20-round drum mag
我手里这个是20发装的弹鼓
It also comes with the 8-round box magazine
它还可以用8发的盒式弹匣
And got some cool targets for you today
今天的靶子也准备了不少独特口味的
See what we can do
咱来看看这货好不好用吧
One thing is really cool
AA-12的亮点其一
It's fully automatic, no select fire
全自动没有快慢机
This is your select fire
手指操纵快慢
That was f**king awesome
真TM爽
And all you do is drop your mag
接下来 换下
throw a new magazine in
换上新的就可以了
And one of the cool things is you got many different kinds of ammunitions
AA-12的亮点其二 它可以使用各种功能的霰弹
for anti-personnel you have a round, for long range you have a round
反步兵来一发 长距离来一发
even for anti-vehicle
连反器材的都有
It works out very nice
用得十分舒心
Let see if we can step up a notch
咱们现在玩点高级的
One of the really cool things about the AA-12
AA-12的亮点其三
is door breaching
专业开锁
Normally, you got one guy with the shotgun
通常情况下 一般得让一个人站前面拿喷子
It breaches the door
开了道破了门之后
followed by a team with M4 carbines or MP5s whatever
后面拿M4 MP5的人再跟进去
With this, you are the entire entry team
不过有个这个 你自己就是个小队
You can blow the door out, then go in and deal with the threat
自己把门破了 自己进去解决敌人
Now you got the breaching shotgun here
现在假设你准备用喷子来破门了
You see it got teeth
这种枪枪口都有锯齿
It jams in, not going to slip off
直接卡门上 死死的
Worst case scenario, your goal is to push someone with it and f**k the sh** up
最糟糕的情况你要一枪把门后的人给爆了
But the thing is you never know how many dead bolts are on it
但最大的问题 你不会知道门上有多少把锁
This one is on I swear, normally, it is
这里一般都会锁上
And there can be one here, here, here, here
但这 这 这 这 都有可能上锁
The AA-12 doesn't matter
AA-12早就看穿了一切
AA-12根本不吃这一套
The entire inside of the door is gone
整个门框都没有了
It doesn't matter what's there
不管它上了多少锁
There's nothing left
全都废了
Okay I got another drum and I will show you one more thing
我刚换了个弹鼓 再给你们演示个情况
Just in case, maybe you got some midgets who're going in on your entry team
万一你有几个地精啦之类的 特别矮的队友的话呢
You can just saw the door in half
直接可以把门锯开来
That's right down in the middle
从正中间
There's no more door
连门都不剩了
You kick the bottom in
你只要把下半边一脚踹开
And everyone goes in
大家就能进来了
Okay, you've seen one AA-12
刚你们看到了一把AA-12
Now you're gonna get to see two AA-12s
现在给你们看两把
There's no more deadly weapon systems in the world
两把AA-12加一个毛子
than a Russian with two AA-12s
可比两把折凳加一个城管还要恐怖
真可以算得上人类史上的终极武器
And keep in mind, don't try this at home
记住 不要随意模仿哟
I'm a professional Russian
本人可是专业的俄国人
So let's get a couple more shots
咱们再去打点别的
And have a little more fun
好好玩玩
So obviously, it's a military shotgun
很显然这把枪是给军警设计的
but if you want to take it to bird hunting
但想拿着去打鸟的话
Pull
放
You can do that
也不成问题
So with any weapon system
不管什么武器
you're not always gonna be firing it in your backyard
你不能指望像我一样只在家院子里打打
You're gonna be SEAL teams coming out of the ocean
比方说海豹突击队得要潜水
You are going to be going to a jungle
进深山老林
You can drop it in the river
或者丢到河里面
But with the AA-12, it doesn't matter
但AA-12说这些都是小case
I've got it completely submerged in water
我已经把它完全泡水里
It's been there for about 10 minutes
差不多10分钟了
We're going to pull it out and see how it operates
咱直接拿出来看它还能不能工作
Drop the mag, throw another one in and it's good to go
换下换上 一点问题没有
So you see how reliable this weapon system is
可见它的可靠性
You can do ANYTHING to it and it doesn't matter
怎么SM它都没问题
It works every time
性♂能保证
One of the really cool things about the AA-12
AA-12还有一个亮点
is that it has absolutely no recoil
一点后坐力都没有
You got very, very little
几乎感受不到
There's a complete spring system back here that absorbs all the shock
这里的弹簧复进系统可以吸收掉所有的后座力
So anyone can operate this weapon
谁都可以用
A child can operate it
小朋友都能用
Check this out
瞧好
Nothing to it
没什么大不了的
Hope you enjoyed the video my friends
本期节目到此为止了
This one is pretty expensive to me
玩这把枪花了不少银子
But I think it's worth it
但个人觉得花得值
And as always, have a nice day
还是那句老话，have a nice day